Oh, hey! How was your audition?
왔어? 오디션 잘 했어?
I'm sorry, do I know you?
죄송하지만 누구시죠?
What are you doing?
뭐 하는 거야?
Practicing blowing you off.
I'm gonna be a big movie star!
무시하는 거 연습이야
난 대스타가 될 거야!
You got it?
배역 땄어?
-Not yet, but the audition went great!
-What's it for?
- 아직, 그런데 오디션은 잘 봤어
- 무슨 역이야?
A big-budget period movie about
three Italian brothers...
막대한 예산의 시대극인데
이태리인 삼형제가
who come to America at the turn
of the century. It's classy.
19세기 말 미국으로 오는
내용이야, 고전이지
The director's supposed to be
the next-next Martin Scorsese.
감독이 차 차세대의
마틴 스코세지래
The "next-next"?
'차 차세대'?
A guy from Chicago's supposed to be
the next Martin Scorsese.
어떤 시카고 출신 감독이
차세대 마틴 스코세지고
This guy's right after him.
이 사람이 그 다음이래
Hello?
여보세요?
Joey, it's Estelle. I just talked to
the casting people. They loved you!
조이, 에스텔이야, 그쪽에서
자네가 마음에 든다는군
They loved me!
내가 마음에 든대!
They want to see you again tomorrow.
내일 좀 보자더군
-My God!
-There's just one thing.
- 우와!
- 한 가지 문제가 있는데
Do you have a problem
with full-frontal nudity?
자네 완전 누드 장면
어떻게 생각하나?
Are you kidding me? I never
rent a movie without it!
그거 없는 영화는
빌려보지도 않는 걸요
Oh.
아
Okay, let me call you back.
제가 다시 전화 드리죠
-What's the matter?
-They want me naked in the movie.
- 왜 그래?
- 누드 장면이 있대
-Wow!
-I know.
- 와!
- 그러게
-My grandmother's gonna see this.
-Grandma's gonna have to get in line.
- 할머니도 보실 텐데
- 줄 서셔야 할 걸
The One With Ross and Monica's Cousin
The One With
Ross and Monica's Cousin
The wedding's so close.
Are you nervous?
결혼식 다가오니
긴장되겠다?
Yeah, but I also can't
wait till it's over.
그래, 빨리 끝났음 좋겠어
We have a pact not to have sex
again until the wedding.
결혼식 때까지
잠자리 안 하기로 했거든
'잠자리 안 하기'라
A "no sex" pact, huh?
난 미국의 모든 여자들과
그러기로 했는데
I have one of those with
every woman in America.
손님 침실 정리하는 거
좀 도와줄래?
Will you give me a hand
making up the guest bedroom?
사촌 캐시가
며칠 와 있기로 했어
Cousin Cassie's staying with us
for a few days.
캐시? 와, 걔 못 본지
진짜 오래됐다
Cassie? I haven't seen her
in, like, forever.
아직도 바비 인형
가지고 다닐까?
I wonder if she still carries
a Barbie everywhere?
- 걘 25살이야
- 그래서? 난 아직도...
-She's 25 years old.
-So? I still..
네 말이 맞다
You're probably right.
Phoebe, can I talk to you
over here for a second?
피비, 조용히 할
얘기가 있는데
눈치챘어
Subtle, guys.
뭐?
What?
깜짝 결혼 축하 파티
준비하는 거잖아
I know you're planning my
surprise bridal shower.
그래, 그럼 망치지 말고
모르는 척 해라
Okay, well, don't ruin it.
Just play along, at least.
알았어, 미안해
Okay. Sorry.
파티 열어줘야 돼?
We have to throw her a shower?
영화 어떻게 하기로 했어?
What'd you decide to do
about the movie?
모르겠어
I don't know.
포르노 영화도 아니고
진지하고 제대로 된 영화야
It's not like it's porn.
This is a serious, legitimate movie.
누드도 스토리 전개상
중요하고
Nudity's really important
to the story.
넌 포르노 볼 때도 그러잖아
That's what you say about porn.
2차 오디션 가지 말까 봐
Maybe I shouldn't go on the callback.
가야 돼, 유명 배우도
누드 장면 다 하잖아
No, you should. A lot of major
actors do nude scenes.
스타가 될 기회야
The chance to star in a movie?
Come on!
맞아, 누드도 한 장면 뿐이고
꽤 멋있겠더라고
That's true. And I'm only naked in
one scene. It sounds really great.
내 배역은 가톨릭 신잔데
유태인 여자와 사랑에 빠져
My character's Catholic. He falls
in love with a Jewish girl.
도망가다 큰 비를
만나서 피하려고
We run away and get caught
in a big rainstorm.
농장에 들어갔다 서로
옷을 벗기고 껴안는 거야
We go into a barn, undress each other
and hold each other.
아주 로맨틱하지
It's really sweet and tender.
게다가 다들
네 거시기도 보고!
Plus, everyone will see your thing!
언제 파티 열지?
When can we have this shower?
모니카가 너무 바빠서
이틀밖에 시간이 안 되는데
She has so much going on,
we have only two options.
- 금요일 괜찮고
- 이틀 뒤잖아
-We have Friday.
-That's just two days away.
- 다른 날은 언제야?
- 어제
-What is the other option?
-Yesterday.
어제였음 다 끝난 거네!
If we make it yesterday, we're done!
불가능해
금요일에도 못 해
It's impossible.
We can't do this by Friday.
장소도 찾아야 하고
사람도 초대하고 음식에다
We have to find a place,
invite people, get food.
할 일이 너무 많아
There's too much to do.
- 도저히 못 해!
- 진정해!
-We cannot do it!
-Calm down!
그래, 미안해, 네 말이 맞아
Okay. I'm sorry, you're right.
I'm sorry.
진정하라구, 이 여자야!
Just calm down, woman!
피비, 난 진정했어
Phoebe, I already did.
좋아, 그럼 내가
진정해야겠다
All right, then I need to calm down.
계획만 잘 세우면
할 수 있어
I think we can do this
if we just get organized.
이틀 남았으니
결정을 빨리 해야 돼
We have two days to plan this party.
We need to make fast decisions.
어디서 할까?
Where will we have it?
-Here. What time?
-4:00. Food?
- 여기, 몇 시?
- 네 시, 음식은
- 핑거 샌드위치와 차
- 좋아! 모니카답다
-Finger sandwiches and tea.
-Great! Very Monica.
- 그리고 칠리!
- 그건 좀 심했다
-And chili!
-You went one too far.
- 꽃 아니면 풍선?
- 둘 다
-Flowers or balloons?
-Both.
- 돈은 우리가 내고?
- 아니
-We're paying for this.
-Neither.
- 주제는 뭘로 할까?
- 육체의 욕망!
-What should we do for a theme?
-Lusts of the Flesh!
- 뭐라고?
- 몰라, 카우보이로 할까?
-What?
-I don't know. Cowboy theme?
결혼 전에 같이 안 자기로
한 거 정말 잘 했지
I'm glad we decided not to sleep
together before the wedding.
그러게, 나도
Oh, boy. Me too.
대판 싸우고 몇 시간만
헤어지는 건 어떨까?
I was thinking, say we had a big fight,
and broke up for a few hours.
Technically, we could have sex again.
그럼, 다시 잘 수 있잖아
어떻게 생각해
잔소리쟁이 폭군?
What do you think,
bossy and domineering?
결혼 취소야
지저분한 애송이
The wedding's off,
sloppy and immature.
That's me. Come on.
그래 좋아, 가자
잠깐, 캐시가 있잖아
점심 같이 먹기로 했어
Wait. Cassie's in the guest room.
We're going to lunch.
어디로 보내 버려
강박증 꽥꽥이!
Get rid of her, obsessive and shrill!
꽥꽥이? 결혼 다시 유효야
Shrill? The wedding is back on.
무슨 소리 들렸는데
그쪽이 챈들러군요
I thought I heard voices.
You must be Chandler.
- 만나서 반가워요
- 나도 반가워요
-Hi. Nice to meet you.
-Nice to meet you too.
- 준비됐어?
- 응
-So, ready to go?
-Yeah.
- 챈들러?
- 좀 있다 얘기해
-Chandler?
-I'll be right with you.
- 캐시, 오빠 집에 좀 가있자
- 왜?
-Cassie needs to stay at your place.
-Why?
글쎄 이 변태 아저씨가
눈을 떼질 못 하잖아
Because "Pervie Perverson" here
can't stop staring at her.
챈들러, 걘 우리 사촌이야!
Chandler, she's our cousin!
안 쳐다봤어
열심히 듣는 거였지
I wasn't staring.
I was listening intently.
난 남의 말을
잘 듣거든, 잘 봐
It's called being a good
conversationalist. Watch.
무슨 말이든 해 봐
Say something.
거기보다 좀 더
아래쪽을 쳐다봤네요
You were staring about eight inches
south of there.
좋아, 우리집에
있으라고 해
Fine. She can stay at my place.
What does Cassie look like now?
캐시 많이 달라졌어?
마릴린 숙모랑 똑같아
Exactly like Aunt Marilyn.
This Aunt Marilyn,
is she coming to the wedding?
그 마릴린 숙모란 분은
결혼식에 오셔?
지금 아슬아슬하다
Wafer-thin ice.
안녕하세요
Hey, I'm back.
어서 와요, 조이
Hi, Joey.
Will I read the same scene again?
같은 대사 읽으면 돼요?
오늘 안 와도 된다고
전화했는데 안 받더군요
I tried to call you.
You didn't need to come today.
잘 됐네요
Oh, great.
이 배역엔 내가 적격인데
I'd have been perfect for this part.
잘못된 결정으로 영화를
망치시네요, 그럼!
You made a bad decision and
ruined your movie. Good day!
감독님이 이미 테이프를 보고
마음에 드신다고 했어요
You didn't need to come, because the
director saw your tape and loved it.
연기였어요
End scene.
Wasn't that fun? We did
a little improv there. Yeah!
재미있죠? 방금
즉흥연기 한 거였어요
그러니까 그 말은?
So, you were saying?
감독님이 내일
만나자고 하셔요
The director wants to meet you
tomorrow.
Wow! Sure! That's great.
와! 그럼요! 잘 됐네요
누드 장면 괜찮다고
했다면서요
Your agent said you're okay
with nudity.
네, 그럼요
제대로만 찍으면요
Yeah, sure. As long as
it's handled tastefully.
그리고 농장이 너무
춥지만 않으면
And that barn is not too cold.
좋아요, 한 가지 더요
Perfect. There's one more thing.
It's important to the director that
everything in the movie's authentic.
감독님은 영화에 나오는 게
모두 진짜이길 바라세요
In your love scene with Sarah...
사라와의 러브씬에서
she talks about how she's never
seen a naked man who wasn't Jewish.
사라가 유태인이 아닌 남자의
벗은 몸은 처음 봤다고 해요
그래서...
So...
So... what?
그래서...뭐요?
그래서 감독님이
이 역을 맡은 사람은
So, the director is insisting
that whoever play that part...
진짜로, 육체적으로
be authentically, anatomically...
유태인이 아니길 바래요
무슨 말인지 알아요?
not Jewish.
You know what I'm saying?
네!
Yes!
아뇨, 뭔데요?
No. What?
이태리 가톨릭 이민자는
그 당시에는...
An Italian Catholic immigrant
at this time would not be....
성인식 안 했다고요?
Bar mitzvah-ed?
- 이 역을 따려면...
- 했으면 안 돼
-To get this part, you can't be..
-No.
But you are?
넌 했는데
-You told them you weren't?
-That's right.
- 안 했다고 했어?
- 맞아
Wow!
와!
It's definitely all gone?
There's nothing there to work with?
전부 다 자른 거야?
아무것도 안 남았어?
-What were you thinking?
-I don't know. I just want this part.
- 무슨 생각으로 그랬어?
- 몰라, 역이 너무 탐나서
오디션에선 무조건
다 한다고 하는 거야
They say no matter what you're asked
during an audition, say yes.
They want you to ride a horse,
say you can.
말 탈줄 아냐고 하면
안다고 하고
You figure out how to do it later.
나중에 배우는 거지
This is not like learning to ride
a horse. This is like learning to...
말 타는 거하고 같아?
이건 다시 거북이 목이
grow a turtleneck.
자라나는 것과 같은데
I know, okay? Tomorrow,
when I go meet the director...
나도 알아, 내일 감독을
만나기로 했는데
I have to take my clothes off so
they can see what my body looks like.
옷을 다 벗어야 돼
내 몸을 보겠대
Oh, my God. What are you gonna do?
맙소사, 너 어쩔 거야?
I have to call my agent and
tell her I can't do the part.
에이전트한테 전화해서
못 한다고 해야지
Unless...
아니면...
Unless what?
아니면 뭐?
This may sound crazy, but there may
be something we could...
황당하게 들리겠지만 뭔가
fashion.
만들 수 있을지도
-Like what?
-Well, I'm not sure yet.
- 뭐를?
- 아직 잘 모르지만
Off the top of my head,
I'm thinking...
지금 생각으론
양면 테이프와
소시지면 될 것 같은데
double-sided tape
and some sort of luncheon meat.
I've got a great idea for party
favors for the shower.
파티 손님 선물로
아주 기막힌 아이디어가 있어
We get mahogany boxes and
carve everyone's names in them.
마호가니 박스를 사서
모두의 이름을 새기고
안에 각자의 탄생석을
넣는 거야
Then inside is each person's
individual birthstone.
Okay. Okay.
좋아, 좋아
You take care of that.
그건 네가 책임져
파티는 내일인데
초청자 명단도 아직 없어
Meanwhile, the party's tomorrow
and we don't have a guest list.
Okay. Who do we know that's coming?
Me. Are you?
좋아, 누가 오는데?
나하고, 너 올 거야?
- 얘들아
- 어서 와, 무슨 일이야?
-Hey.
-Hey, what's up?
I'm making something for Joey.
Can I raid your fridge?
조이한테 뭐 만들어 줄 건데
냉장고 좀 뒤져도 돼?
Have at it.
맘대로 해
All right. Turkey? That won't work.
좋아, 칠면조? 안 되고
Cheese? That won't work.
치즈? 이것도 안 되고
올리브 덩어리? 안 되지
Olive loaf? I hope that won't work.
샌드위치 만들어 주게?
Are you making him a sandwich?
아니, 쌈 비슷한 거지
No, it's more like a wrap.
Okay, so I'm gonna go, guys.
좋아, 난 가 볼게
So you can get back to deciding on
what to get me for a present!
내 선물 뭐 줄건지
상의하던 거 계속해
선물도 사 줘야 돼?
We have to get her a present?
Okay, but look. Look at what I got.
내가 뭐 갖고 있나 봐봐
It's her address book.
We have a guest list.
모니카 주소록이야
손님 명단 해결됐어
You're amazing. Did you pull
that out of her purse?
너 대단하다
핸드백에서 슬쩍한 거야?
Uh-huh. And a little seed money
for the party.
응, 파티 자금도 마련했고
Cassie?
캐시니?
Hey, Ross!
안녕, 오빠!
It's been so long!
정말 오랜만이다!
Last time I saw you...
마지막으로 봤을 때
you were setting up your tent
in line for Return of the Jedi.
오빠가 제다이의 귀환 보려고
텐트치고 줄 서 있었지
맞아
So you did see me that day.
Because it seemed like you didn't.
그 날 나 봤구나
못 봤는 줄 알았는데
-Yeah, sorry about that.
-It's okay. Come on in.
- 미안해, 모른 척 해서
- 괜찮아, 들어와
Thanks for letting me stay here.
Monica's place was nice.
지내게 해줘서 고마워
모니카네 집도 좋은데
약혼자가 하도 쳐다봐서
But her fiance sure stares a lot.
Oh, my God! You do a great Chandler!
어머나! 챈들러 흉내 잘 내네
I have a knack for impressions.
내가 흉내는 잘 내거든
Maybe after we get re-acquainted
you could do me.
그럼 조금 있다
나 한 번 해 봐
Yeah. No!
그래, 싫어!
어때, 그...
How you doing on that...
핫도그?
hot dog?
- 다 먹었어
- 다행이다
-I'm all done.
-Thank God.
마지막으로 같이 놀았던 게
해변 별장에서였지
The last time we hung out was when
our parents rented that beach house.
내가 널 넘어뜨리고
울 때까지 간지럽힌 거 기억나?
Remember the time I pinned you down
and tickled you until you cried?
이젠 그러기엔 너무 나이 들었지
We're probably too old to do that now.
그해 여름 늘 기억할 거야
그때 이 주근깨 생겼잖아
I'll always remember that summer.
It's when I got all these freckles.
I'll always remember that summer...
나도 그때 늘 기억할 거야
처음으로 우리가
친척이란 거 알았거든
because that's when I realized
that we are related.
It took you that long
to figure it out?
그걸 그때서야 안 거야?
내가 좀 느리잖아
I'm a little slow.
Just as our children would be.
우리 사이의 애도 그렇겠지
-Hi.
- 안녕하세요
안녕하세요? 좋네요
와 주셔서 고마워요
How are you? Good. Hi.
Thanks for coming.
고마워요, 반가워요
Thank you. So nice to see you.
-No, thanks.
-Okay. Hey, Rach?
- 전 됐어요
- 알았어요, 레이첼?
-Yeah?
-Who the hell are all these people?
- 응?
- 이 사람들 누구야?
I don't know.
I called everybody in her book.
몰라, 주소록보고 전화했는데
These are the ones that could
show up on 24 hours' notice.
하루 전에 통보 받고도
올 수 있다고 한 사람들이야
There's a word for people like that:
Losers.
이런 사람들을 뭐라고 하게?
낙오자들
Hi, I'm Rachel. This is Phoebe.
I'm the maid of honor.
전 레이첼이고 여긴 피비예요
전 신부 들러리죠
-How do you know Monica?
-I was her accountant four years ago.
- 모니카는 어떻게 아세요?
- 4년 전 제가 회계를 맡았죠
I'm interested to find out who's been
doing her taxes the last four years.
누가 지난 4년간 모니카 세금을
다뤘는지 궁금하네요
That's great.
잘 됐네요
- 모니카는 언제 와요?
- 저도 몰라요
-When is Monica supposed to get here?
-I don't know.
Excuse us.
잠깐만요
- 너 말 안했어?
- 네가 하기로 했잖아
-You didn't tell her?
-You were supposed to.
네가 모니카한테 연락하고
난 케이크 담당이었지
You were supposed to tell her to come!
I was bringing the cake!
-Fine, I'll go call her.
-And please tell her to bring a cake!
- 알았어, 전화할게
- 케이크 하나 가져오라고 해
We have a lot of options. A number
of prototypes for you to try on.
여러 가지를 만들어 봤으니
한 번 써 봐
Those look great.
다 좋아 보이는데
Okay, this one's a mushroom cap.
This one is made of bologna.
좋아, 이건 버섯
이건 볼로니 소시지
- 이쑤시개?
- 풀이 안 말라서
-The toothpicks?
-Just until the glue dries.
다행이다
Thank God.
이건 좀 실감나는데
잘 상해
These are more realistic,
but perishable.
여기 이건 핑크 세무
좋긴 한데
Over here, we have pink suede,
which is nice.
젖으면 줄어들어
But if it gets wet, it'll shrink.
Maybe we'll just
take that one away.
그럼 그건 빼야지
모피로 만든 것도 있는데
이건 내가 가질 거야
I also did a little something in fur,
but that's really just for me.
한 번 직접 해 봐
그럼 더 잘 알 거야
Why don't you try these on? We'll
get a better idea of what works.
고마워, 넌 정말 좋은 친구고
이건 정말 이상하다
Thanks, you are such a good friend.
And this is so weird.
- 이쑤시개야?
- 응
-Toothpick?
-Yeah.
- 지금은 뭐야?
- 과일 젤리
-What are you trying now?
-The Fruit Roll-up.
- 어때?
- 맛있다
-And?
-Delicious.
잠깐, 잠깐, 드디어 찾았어!
Wait a minute. Wait a minute.
We have a winner!
뭐야? 어느 거야?
What? Which one?
고무찰흙, 괜찮은 걸
The Silly Putty.
Not so silly anymore!
She's your cousin.
얜 네 사촌이야
네가 무슨 생각하는 지
알면 변태라고 할 걸
If she knew what was going on in
your head, she'd think you were sick.
정말 그럴까?
잠시 생각 좀 하자
Or would she?
Let's back up for a second.
She was the one who suggested
opening a bottle of wine.
와인 마시자고
한 것도 캐시였고
조명을 어둡게 한 것도
캐시였고
She was the one who
turned down the lights.
야한 영화 도망자 로간을
빌리자고 한 것도
She was the one that wanted to rent
Logan's Run...
바로 캐시야
the sexiest movie ever.
저 표정 좀 봐
I know that look.
나도 원하고
캐시도 원하잖아
Forget it. I want it. She wants it.
에라 모르겠다
I'm going in.
도대체 무슨 짓이야?
What the hell are you doing?
뭔가 그럴듯한 말을 해
Say something clever.
Okay, doesn't have to be clever.
좋아, 그럴듯하지
않아도 돼
아무 말이라도 괜찮으니 해
Just has to be words. Say some words.
무슨 말이라도 해
Any words will do.
맙소사, 이렇게
Oh, my God, this is the longest...
긴 침묵은 처음이야
that anyone has not talked ever!
이 사태를 더 악화시킬
말은 없으니
There is nothing you could say
to make this worse...
어서 뭐든 말하라고!
so just say something!
섹스를 너무 오래 못했거든
I haven't had sex in a very long time.
차라리 아무 말 마는 건데
Yeah, you really shouldn't
have said anything.
피비? 레이첼? 모니카야
Phoebe? Rachel? It's Monica.
I wonder what you could possibly
need me for on such short notice?
갑자기 날 이렇게
오라고 한 이유가 뭘까?
- 모니카, 미안해
- 뭐가?
-Oh, Monica. We are so sorry.
-For what?
우선, 네 축하 파티
잊어버린 것
First, for forgetting to
throw you a bridal shower.
그리고 널 초대하는 걸
잊어버린 것
Then, forgetting to invite you to it.
벌써 끝났어?
You already had it?
네 주소록 보고
사람들을 불렀는데
We called everyone in your phone book.
A bunch of people came.
네가 오는 동안
다 가버렸어
It took us so long to get you here
that they had to leave.
깜짝 놀랄만한
멋진 파티를 해주고 싶었는데
We wanted to throw you a big surprise
and a great shower.
다 물 건너갔어
Now you don't have either.
다 우리 탓이야
We ruined everything.
아냐, 잠깐, 그렇지 않아
너희들 정말 고마워
No, wait a minute, that's not true.
What you did was really sweet.
- 차라리 잘 됐어
- 무슨 소리야?
-It kind of works out for the best.
-What do you mean?
내가 정말 사랑하는 사람들과
시간을 보낼 수 있고
Now I get to spend my shower
with the only people I really love.
좋아하지도 않는 사람
안 만나고 선물은 챙겼잖아
I get all those presents without
talking to people I don't even like!
- 서프라이즈
- 서프라이즈, 모니카
-Surprise.
-Surprise, Monica.
이 사람 고향이
나폴리라고 하셨죠?
What's cool is, the character
is from Naples, right?
제 가족도 나폴리 출신이죠
My whole family's from Naples.
좋아요, 이제 들을 걸
다 들었으니...
That's great. Okay. I've heard
everything I need to hear...
이제 할 일은...
We just need to, uh...
레슬리?
Leslie?
- 조이, 좀 어색하네요
- 괜찮아요
-Joey, this is the awkward part.
-Hey, right. Not a problem.
저도 이해해요
I totally understand you need to...
몸에 상처나 문신이
없는 지도 봐야 하실 거고
make sure I don't have any
horrible scars or tattoos.
Don't you worry.
걱정 마세요
전 숨길 게 없어요
I have nothing to hide.
So, there you go. That's me.
여기요, 접니다
100% 자연산이죠
One hundred-percent natural.
이런 적 한 번도 없었는데
I tell you, that has never
happened before.
캐시, 뭐 불편한 거 없어요?
Cassie, are you finding
everything okay?
Yeah. Thanks for
letting me stay here.
네, 지내게 해줘서 고마워요
Oh, it's no problem.
별소릴 다 하네요
What?
왜 그래요?
Say something. Say anything.
무슨 말이든 해
데이트 신청해
네 사촌도 아닌데 뭘!
Ask her out! She's not your cousin!